Hey, I'm Tobi.
こんにちは トビーです
And I'm Ben.
ベンです
And we are software engineers at Mercedes-Benz,
Mercedes-Benz のソフトウェアエンジニアで
who work in the behavior planning team.
動作プランニングチームで働いています
The behavior planning team is responsible for providing guidance to
動作プランニングチームの責任は どのような種類の操作でトラジェクトリーを計画する必要があるかについて
the trajectory planner about what sorts of maneuvers they should plan trajectories for.
トラジェクトリープランナーにガイダンスを提供することです
If you think about the over all flow of data in
コントロールする一番速い時間スケールでの
a self-driving car operating on the fastest time scales you have control.
自動運転車の操作のデータのフロー全体を考えると
And with a slightly lower frequency than that you have Sensor Fusion.
また センサー フュージョンでの頻度よりも少し少ない頻度で
Just lower than that you have localization and
ローカライゼーションとトラジェクトリープランニングよりも少し低くなります
trajectory planning which you learn more about in a next lesson.
これらは次のレッスンで学習します
Next is Prediction which you just learned about.
次が 今学習した予測です
And then at the top of this diagram is behavior planning with the lowest update rate.
この図の一番上が 一番低い更新率の動作プランニングです
The inputs to behavior planning come from
動作プランニングの情報は
the prediction module and the localization module.
予測モジュールとローカライゼーションモジュールからきています
Both of which get their inputs from the sensor fusion.
それらの両方の情報は センサー関数からきています
And the output from the behavior module goes directly to the trajectory planner.
動作モジュールからの出力は 直接トラジェクトリープランナーにいきます
Which also takes input from prediction and
予測とローカライゼーションからの情報を使用し
localization so that it can send trajectories to the motion controller.
トラジェクトリーをモーションコントローラーに送信できます
Everything inside of this box is the focus of
このボックス内のものは全て、このコースで着目していることであり、
this course and is commonly referred to as Path Planning.
一般的にパスプランニングの中で参照されます
In this lesson, you will learn what exactly has to
このレッスンでは この比較的長いスパンで
happen in this comparatively long time span.
発生しなければならないことを学習します
But intuitively this longtime span comes from
でも
the fact that the behavior plan has to incorporate a lot of
動作プランは10 秒以上の順序で
data to make decisions about
極めて長い範囲について決定を行うために多くのデータに組み込む必要がある
fairly long time horizons in the order of 10 seconds or even more.
という事実から 直感的なこの長いスパンはきています
We will start by doing a brief introduction where
動作プランナーへの入力と
you'll learn more about the details of the inputs and
出力の詳細について学習し
outputs to behavior planner and understand
動作プランニングモジュールが解決すると予測する問題を
what problems a behavior planning module is expected to solve.
理解する簡単な概要説明を始めます
Next, we will talk about
次に 動作プランを実装するテクニックの 1 つとして
Finite State Machines as one technique for implementing a behavior plan.
Finite State Machines について説明します
Followed by a more in-depth look at
続いて 行動に関するレベルを決定するために使用する
the Cost Functions we will use to actually make behavioral level decisions.
コスト関数をもっと詳しく見ていきます
But first let's spend some time looking at the inputs
でも まず 作業する入力と生成する出力について
we would be working with and the outputs we will be generating.
少し見ていきたいと思います